In Secret is a drama, thriller, crime film directed by Charlie Stratton.
In 1860s Paris, a young woman, Therese, is trapped in a loveless marriage to
the sickly Camille by her domineering aunt, Madame Raquin.
She spends her days behind the counter of a small shop and her evenings
watching Madame play dominos with an eclectic group.
After she meets her husband’s alluring friend, Laurent, she embarks on
an illicit affair that leads to tragic consequences.
Based on Emile Zola’s novel, Thérèse Raquin.
Thérèse Raquin, played by Elizabeth Olsen.
Camille Raquin, played by Tom Felton.
Madame Raquin, played by Jessica Lange.
Olivier, played by Matt Lucas.
Laurent LeClaire, played by Oscar Isaac.
Suzanne, played by Shirley Henderson.
In Secret (also known as Thérèse) is a 2013 American erotic thriller
romance film written and directed by Charlie Stratton.
Based on Émile Zola's classic 1867 novel Thérèse Raquin and the 2009 stage play by the same name penned
by Neal Bell, the film stars Elizabeth Olsen, Tom Felton, Oscar Isaac and Jessica Lange.
It was screened in the Special Presentation section at the
2013 Toronto International Film Festival.
The film received a regional release on February 21, 2014.
The tone is emotional and intense.